https://www.tribalwar.com/privacy.php

Tribalwar
Home | Submit News | Bump News | Cloud | Find News | Staff | Feedback | Donate | Supporters | Blog | Wiki | Forums
Login | Register
Search
Privacy Statement
Information Collection
When registering for TribalWar.Com services, we ask that you provide specific personal information such as an e-mail address
and birth date.
TribalWar.Com uses this information to ensure compliance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)
as well as for various administrative purposes.
Some of this information may appear in your posts or online profile at TribalWar.
If you wish to control public access to this information,
please update your profile with your customizable privacy settings.
Log Files
Our webserver collects data about our visitors and logs this information on our server.
This data includes information such as IP addresses,
browser software, and referring pages.
This data is used by TribalWar for administrative purposes and to collect demographics about our user base.
Personally Indentifiable Information
We DO NOT rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people, nonaffiliated companies, advertisers, or Third Parties.
Legal Disclaimer
TribalWar reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law or hen we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.
Pursuant to Section 230 of the Communications Decency Act, TribalWar shall not be treated or held liable as the publisher or speaker of any information provided by another information content provider.
User posted content on the website is authored by individual members, and is not screened or approved by TribalWar before becoming publicly posted. All messages express the views of the author, and TribalWar will not be held responsible for the content of any message.
Please keep in mind that any personal information you elect to post on TribalWar
is accessible to a wide, public collection of people. TribalWar shall not be held responsible for any damages or losses incurred due to information
posted herein and liability for content posted on TribalWar lies with the individual authors of said content.
Content © 1999-2020, TribalWar.Com, All rights reserved. | Advertise on TribalWar | Privacy Statement
